Paul Muldoon papers, 1939-2010
Emory University
- Writings by Muldoon, circa 1960s-2004, Series 2; Boxes 8-30, 66-84 and OP 2-9, 163-167
  - Poetry, circa 1960s-2003, Subseries 2.1; Boxes 8-23, 66-73 and OP 2-4, 163, 165
    - "White Telephone," single holograph draft (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - "Early Poems"
    - "The Affair," single corrected typescript (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - "Aisling," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - "Alba," single corrected typescript, two-sided (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - "Amazonia," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - "America," two typescripts [See also variant title "Stampede" (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - "Armageddon," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Armageddon typescript pamphlet with corrections, including "Armageddon" [See also Mules: "Armageddon, Armageddon"], "The Field Hospital," "Sir Walter," and "Stampede," with multiple typescript drafts of "Armageddon" (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - "Back," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - "Badger," single holograph draft, backed with unknown poem (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - "The Ballad of Moll Pulldown," two typescripts with minimal holograph corrections [See also Lines for the Girl Who Ate the Apples] (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - "Balloon Talk" single typescript (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - "Balls," single typescript, title crossed out [See also "The Girls in the Poolroom"] (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - "The Bed Not Slept In," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - "Belfast," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - "Belfast to Dublin" and "Boogie" and "Cat's Cradle" and "Fancy Dress," single corrected typescript, dated May 2, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - "The Big House," single corrected typescript (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - "Bitters," single corrected typescript (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - "Blues for a Boy," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - "Bolg Chonaill," single typescript (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - "Bronagh," multiple typescript drafts (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - "Caravan" and "Ropemakers," two-page corrected manuscript (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - "The Castrati," two typescript drafts with some holograph corrections (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "Ceann Cait," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "Central Park," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Centre Piece," two typescript drafts with short holograph note (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "The Charcoal Burner," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "Cheesecake," multiple typescript drafts with some holograph corrections (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - " Considering the Islands," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - "A Conversation With Yeats," single corrected typescript [See also "The Groundsman"] (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - "The Country Club," two corrected typescripts, one backed with unidentified fragment ["Hazel"] and one with several lines of "The Country Club" on reverse (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - "Cuba," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - "Dandelion Clock," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Dánta typescript packet of Irish poems, including "Eagmais," "Scoite," "Bolg Chonaill," "Idir," and "Ceann Cait"; two complete packets and first page ("Eagmais" to "Bolg Chonaill") of another 14 "The Digger looked right through me.. ." single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - "The Disappearance of the Lark," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - "Dixon on Tory," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "[Dream in] The Green Room," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - "The Drowned Blackbird, after Mac Cuarta," single typescript with holograph notes (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - "The Ducking Stool," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - "The Dugout," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - "Eagmais," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - "Emblem," single typescript backed with fragment of Oisin play (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - "The Enquiry," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - "Evensong," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - "A Flock of Robins," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - "For a Wife," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - "For Seamus Heaney, Who Gives Horses," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - "Fox Sleep," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - ["FX Sea and Wind... ."], single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Gazelle Boy," single photocopied typescript (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - "Genealogy," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - "Gifts," single xeroxed typescript, crossed out (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - "The Glass Boat," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - "Going Away," single typescript with minimal holograph corrections (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - "The Goods," two corrected typescripts (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - "Green Apples," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - "Greim," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - "The Groundsman," single typescript [See also "A Conversation With Yeats"] (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - "Hairy Mary," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - "The Hawk in Armagh," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - "Heirloom," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - "History," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - "Hitler," two typescripts, one with holograph corrections (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - "Home," two corrected typescripts, one page backed with page from Oisin play (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - "Homecomings," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - "I know a boy.. ." single typescript (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - "iD," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - "Idir," single typescript [See also Dánta] (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - "Idir" and "Ceann Cait," single typescript with "Ceann Cait" crossed out [See also Dánta] (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Imreanna, title page (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - "The Inheritors," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - "The Initiation," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - "Ireland," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - "January," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - "Kate Whiskey," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - "The Kiss," two typescript drafts, one with holograph corrections (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - "Lammas," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - "The Lap Dog," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Lines for the Girl Who Ate the Apples, multiple typescripts, including "Saga," "The Music Lesson," "The Sharping Stone," "Cheesecake," "Storm People," "Faces," "The Apartment," "On a Dog of Unlike Eyes," "Lines for the Girl Who Ate the Apples," "Surprise, Surprise," "Mermaid Purse," "The Pink Tandem," "Theo," "The Man Without a Name" and "The Ballad of Moll Pulldown" (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - "Lines for the Girl Who Ate the Apples," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - "Linnets," two holograph drafts (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - "Little Skellig," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - "The Long Weekend," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - "II: 'Look,' she said.. ." single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - "Lord Hawhaw," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - "Lough Derg, 1969," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - "Lull," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - "Lying on a Sheet of Glass in T.'s Garden," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - "The Man Without a Name," single typescript with holograph note (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - "Marble Cake," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - "Marble Orchard III: I used to think.. ." single typescript with minimal corrections (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - "Mercy" [tentatively titled "When the Bough Breaks"], two corrected typescript drafts (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - "Mercy was thirteen.. ." single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - "Mermaid Purses," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - "Mileages," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - "Missing Persons," holograph draft and single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - "Mouth to Hand," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - "The Moy Clock," two typescript drafts (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Mules, early tables of contents and related holograph notes (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - "The Music Lesson," single typescript (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - "Must," single corrected typescript (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - "Ned Skinner," two corrected typescripts, one with holograph Mules table of contents on back (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - "Nettle Soup," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - "No Longer Children" and "Song," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - "IV: On a Dog of Unlike Eyes," single typescript [See also Lines for the Girl Who Ate the Apples] (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Other Poems, single typescript title page (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - "The Other Woman," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "Our Lady of Ardboe," multiple corrected typescripts (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Palm Sunday," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Perfect Strangers, single typescript title page (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - "Perhaps," single typescript crossed out and dated August 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - "The Pink Tandem," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - "Please Remember This," single holograph draft (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - "Poetry," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - "Prologue to the Loyalist's Tale," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - "Promises, Promises," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - "Ra," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - "Rabies," two typescript drafts with minimal holograph corrections (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - "Rapunzel," single corrected typescript with corrected photocopy (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - "Recent Reading," single holograph draft (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - "Rodgers at Loughgall," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - "Saga," single typescript with minimal holograph corrections (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - "Sally," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - "The Salt-Lick," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - "Sappho on Lesbos," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - "Scoite," single typescript [See also Dánta] (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - "Serenade," single typescript [See also "Together We Fall"] (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - "The Sharping Stone," single typescript [See also Lines for the Girl Who Ate the Apples] (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - "Sir Walter," single typescript with title page (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - "Sister and Seascape," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - "Skara Brae," single holograph draft with "Poteen" and unidentified poem on back (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - "Small Talk," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - "A Song for Simon," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - "Spirit of Dawn," single photocopy of typescript (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - "Stampede," multiple corrected typescript drafts [See also variant title "America"] (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - "Star Imagery," single page holograph notes (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - "Storm People," single typescript with minimal holograph note (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - "Surprise, Surprise," single corrected typescript and holograph notes (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Sweet Nothings, typescript and holograph title pages with holograph notes (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - "Tableau," two corrected typescript drafts (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - "The Telephones," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - "Telling it like it is.. ." single typescript (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - "The whole is.. ." single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - "Theo," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - "There has been a change.. ." single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - "These people have shut.. ." single typescript (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - "Thistles," single typescript with minimal holograph correction (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - "Threshing Day," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - "Together We Fall," two-page corrected prose typescript, dated "Easter 1970" [See also "Serenade"] (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - "Truce," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - "Tschiffley's Ride," two typescript drafts, one backed with page from Oisin play (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Two, typescript title page (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - "Uncle Pat," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - "The Upriver Incident," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - "Vandals," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - "Vespers," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - The Walled Garden: Love Poems, incomplete typescript with holograph corrections (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - "Waterskiers -- Lough Neagh," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - "The Weepies," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - "Wildtrack," single corrected typescript (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - "Wolf Children," single typescript (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - "You remember Churchill.. ." single holograph draft (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - "Your face is the nought.. ." single typescript (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Your Place or Mine, typescript title page (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Unidentified prose fragments (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Photocopies of typescripts, including "Armageddon," "The Narrow Road to the Deep North," "Duffy's Circus," "Mules," "A Summer Night," "Ma," and "Cass and Me" (original grouping preserved) (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Typed epigraphs from Tennyson, Cochise, and Black Elk, with holograph notes (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Miscellaneous holograph notes (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous tables of contents drafts and lists of potential places for publication of poems (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Photocopies of a timeline re: Aughrim and "A Ballad of Master McGrath" (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Knowing My Place (1971) [See Early Poems]
    - New Weather (1973) [See also Early Poems]
    - New Weather, corrected typescript draft (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - New Weather, typescript with minimal holograph notes re: pagination (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - New Weather, page proofs (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - New Weather, sheet proofs with holograph corrections and envelope from Faber and Faber (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - New Weather, sheet proofs with minimal holograph corrections (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Spirit of Dawn (1975) [See Early Poems]
    - Mules (1977) [Muldoon's original folder title: "Mostly Mules"]
    - "The Apartment," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - "The Apartment" and "The Riders," typescript draft with holograph note [See also "The Centaurs" and "The Riders"] (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Armageddon, Armageddon" [variant titles "A Summer Night" and "Mouse Island"], multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - "At Master McGrath's Grave," single typescript title page (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "The Bay of Pigs" [variant title for "Cuba"], typescript draft (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "The Big House," multiple typescript drafts with title page (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "The Big House," single corrected typescript with "Ned Skinner" on back (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "Big Liz" [variant title "A Northern Club"], multiple holograph drafts (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - "Boom," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Brides," single corrected typescript (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - "Bronagh," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - "Cass and Me," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - "The Centaurs," single typescript [See also "The Riders"] (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - "Cheesecake," single corrected typescript (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "Cider," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - "Corn Fiddler," single typescript (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - "The Country Club," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "Cuba," [See "Bay of Pigs"]
    - "Drifters: Gazelle Boy," single typescript title page (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - "Drifters:[vz?]," single typescript title page (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - "Drifters: Gazelle Boy" and "Vaquero," single typescript with minimal holograph corrections [See also "Icon"] (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "The Ducking Stool," single typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - "Duffy's Circus," single typescript (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - "Dumb Waitrr [Sic] Hectoring," single typescript title page (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - "Epona," [variant titles "Pegasus" and "In Parson's Meadow"], multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - "The Girls in the Poolroom," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - "The Glass Boat," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - "The Harvest Bow," single corrected typescript (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - "Icon," single typescript [See also "The Rucksack" and "Drifters: Gazelle Boy"] (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - "The Lament for Art O'Leary" and/or "Keen," holograph titles (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - "The Lament for Art O'Leary," single typescript title page (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - "Largesse" [variant title for "Psalm" and "The Pink Tandem"], multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - "Linnets," single typescript title page (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - "Ma," single typescript (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - "Martha's Deli," single corrected typescript with one line from "The Rucksack" on back (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - "The Narrow Road to the Deep North," single typescript with title page (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - "Ned Skinner," multiple typescript drafts and holograph notes [See also "The Big House"] (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - "Now we had gathered.. ." single typescript (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - "Once in the New Forest.. ." [variant title "To the Woods"], single typescript (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - "Our Lady of Ardboe," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - "Promises, Promises," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - "The Riders" [variant title "Herman Confer's"], holograph title page [See also "The Centaurs" and "The Apartment] (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - "The Rucksack," holograph and typescript draft with "Icon" on the back [See also "Martha's Deli" (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - "Sir Walter,"single typescript (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - "Spirit of Dawn," single corrected typescript (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - "Stampede," multiple typescript drafts (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - "Stampede" and "Patronage/ The Two Patrons - after the Gaelic," single typescript with minimal holograph corrections (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - "Sullivan's Wife.. ." multiple holograph drafts (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - "The Swing," single corrected typescript (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - "Vaquero," single typescript [See also "Drifters: Gazelle Boy"] (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Notes for publication of Mules poems (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Mules, "final typescript" with some holograph corrections (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Mules, sheet proofs with minimal holograph corrections (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Mules, photocopy of corrected typescript with cardboard folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Mules, multiple typescript title pages (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Mules, two early tables of contents, one with holograph corrections (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Source materials from "Mostly Mules" file (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Why Brownlee Left (1980)
    - Why Brownlee Left, multiple typescript drafts of tables of contents (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - "Immram," incomplete corrected typescript with holograph notes (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Why Brownlee Left, typescript, setting copy with holograph corrections [See also Miscellaneous Poems, circa 1978-1983] (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Various poems written by others about Why Brownlee Left (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Quoof (1983)
    - The More a Man Has, The More a Man Wants [variant title for Quoof], typescript with minimal holograph corrections (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Quoof, corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Quoof, proofs with holograph corrections [See also Miscellaneous Poems, circa 1978-1983] (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Selected Poems, 1968-1983
    - Holograph notes for Selected Poems (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Selected Poems 1968-1983 (Faber edition), corrected typescript with assembled photocopies (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Selected Poems 1968-1983 (Faber edition), page proofs with holograph corrections (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Selected Poems 1968-1983 (Faber edition), drafts of table of contents (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Poems, circa 1978-1983
    - "The Affair," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - "Aftermath," single typescript (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "Anarchy," single corrected typescript [See also "The Groundsman"] (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - "The Apartment," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - "The Bald Patch," (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Big Foot in Death," title pages with holograph notes (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - "Blight," single holograph draft (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - "Bloom Sunday," single typescript (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - "Blossom," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - "The Brothers," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - "A Christmas Truce," single typescript (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - "Edward Kienholz: The State Hospital," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - "Emblem," single holograph draft (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - "The End," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - "Ether," single corrected typescript with title page (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - "The Flight," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - "The Floosies," single typescript with holograph notes (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - "Gathering Mushrooms," early typescript draft, with photocopied clipping (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - "Glanders," single page of holograph notes (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - "The Glass Boat," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - "The Goal," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - "Going Away," single typescript with title crossed out [See also "Promises, Promises"] (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - "The Groundsman," single typescript with holograph notes [See also "Anarchy"] (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - "Her Last Man," multiple typescript drafts [See also "Smalltalk"] (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - "The High Chair," single typescript (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - "High Hedges," single corrected typescript (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - "The Hip-Gatherers," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "The Home," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Initial Deception," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "The intra-uterine device.. ." single corrected typescript [See also "Mushrooms"] (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "James Dixon: The First Tractor That Ever Came to Tory," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "Kiss and Tell," holograph notes, with title page for proposed collection [See also The O-O's Party, Subseries 2.4, Children's Poetry] (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - "Lord Haw-Haw," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Lost Ground," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "The Love Poem," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Missing Persons," multiple typescript drafts (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "The More a Man Has, The More a Man Wants," corrected typescript (circa 73 pages) with complete photocopy of file contents (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - "Mother May Die," single holograph draft (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "The Mushroom House," single holograph draft (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - "The mushroom spawn.. ." single typescript with holograph notes (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - "Mushrooms," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - "My father is listening to the wireless.. ." single typescript (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - ["No Surrender: Plantation"], single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 17)